(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T22:38:49.012728",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Greetings, Cece, my fated rival!
Greetings, Ina, my destined rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured...
...on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
...post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
And thank you AmiAmi for supporting our rivalry,
and for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out their booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou, Biboo!
And all of holoBASE is here with me,
all 14 of us!
holoBASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide,
starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors: 演出による激しい光にご注意ください / 声出しOK
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity
[hololive English 4th Concert: Serendipity]
Sing out boldly again
Continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the cloudy skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up, everyone!
Welcome to holoEN Serendipity!
Wah! I'm glad we're back!
Let's kick off the show with a Myth medley!
Ready? 1, 2, 3!
Showtime, baby! I would say
Today's forecast looks like delay
Rubbing out the scoff, is it really enough?
Spoken but brewing endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Set a fire in the hearth when the PC burns, huh!
Optimistic, focus on a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Still growing stronger than ever and never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freakin' lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers descend, huh
I'm not losing to you young people!
Ignore her! It's a Myth that's priceless, you know!
Spanning new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension
Dancing in flight, we ignite!
Join us while we're celebrating
In the Myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond!
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond
Guiding us endlessly
Will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
We'll always find the way to reunite!
1, 2, 3!
Lights up, let's, let's, let's begin, we'll start
Stage right and shuffle on in
Is everybody ready to steal the show?
We're jumping with joy, let's go!
Curtains up, so cue the band
We'll keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle they'll never forget
We'll hold a party from dusk to dawn
The show will go on and on
Tell them that we're here to stay
And spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway
Gleaming in the spotlight
Get the gang together, we're boogying all night
Ooh! Ooh!
Beaming so bright
Now we're feeling alright
Ah! Ah!
Since the day we met, we've fallen and grown strong
And we'll keep moving right along
So keep on dancing, yeah you fit in
Nothing can stop us, we're a perfect quintet
In harmony no matter where we go
Like it's meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it all springs
Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper "Truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring;
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase, a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah, la-da-da-da-da-da...
I'm always spinning fate
Whoa, yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on,
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string,
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get,
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last.
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh, la-la-la...
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Blazing fire
Can't control it anymore, I'm burning up red
Crazy thoughts filling my head
Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop,
Blazing, boiling, getting hot, it's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart going up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on, I wanna confess, baby, oh baby, I'm getting obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be, wanna be ready for more
Caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire
I'm gonna, wanna turn it up, I'm burning up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm baring my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play a dangerous game
Got your fire running through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turning to ash, breaking me, shaking me, making me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
Driving me, driving me, driving me crazy, telling me, telling me what do you mean
Caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazin' fire
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
I'm only getting started
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazin' fire
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
AutoFister
CCGG madness, Otomos, now listen
CCGG madness, Grems, get in position
CCGG madness, orange plus green division
Ooh, AutoFister
ハイ！ハイ！ CCGG mad fun
Hai! Hai! CCGG mad fun
ハイ！ハイ！ Gremlin automaton
Hai! Hai! Gremlin automaton
ハイ！ハイ！ CCGG mad fun
Hai! Hai! CCGG mad fun
Guten Tag! Do you know where the bathroom is?
I've been walking around all day and I really need to go.
ハイ！ハイ！ Gremlin automaton
Hai! Hai! Gremlin automaton
Uh, no,
but I've seen this new super cute cafe around the corner,
and they sell tea and Baumkuchen!
Sorry, I don't speak German.
Oh?
On this day you are cursed to cope
and keep it in your memory
Oh, come on, you're supposed to hope
and let our brand of madness run its course
Take our hand, let's fly away (Ooh-wee!)
Break a leg, now challenge fate (Yay!)
Quick, before your time's up,
give in and be our playmate
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await (Yay!)
Love yourself, don't be afraid (Ooh-yee!)
Sign just one condition (Ooh-wee!)
Give in, release all inhibition
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, AutoFister
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come, let's play
Come on, LA! We want to hear you shout!
Recently...
I've just been having so much anxiety,
'cause I can't find a single manga that I like, like...
I like so many different genres,
like romance, romance, and romance,
but I still don't know what to do.
Sorry, what were you saying? I was looking at my phone.
Ugh!
Oh, come on, can a girl not hope
to lose your heart in reverie?
There's no way to divert this trope,
so let our brand of madness run its course
Take our hand, let's fly away (Ooh-wee!)
Make a way now, choose a date (Yay!)
Quick, before your time's up,
give in and be our playmate
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await (Yay!)
Love yourself, don't be afraid (Ooh-yee!)
Live up your ambition (Ooh-wee!)
Come on, let go of intuition
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, AutoFister
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come and play
Why do you always yell at me all the time? I just don't get it.
'Cause you're so stupid!
Every time I come to you and I'm trying to be really, really nice,
all you do is talk over me!
Well, maybe you should have something good to say for once!
I have so many good things to say every single day!
Literally not a single time! You drive me insane!
You're so stupid, I can't stand you!
もう一回！
One more time!
All our fun must come to an end,
but at least you've found a friend
So let us play...
...forever
Now, together
Take our hand, let's fly away
Turn around and let us stay
Sign just one condition
Come on, join in our sacred mission
Fly away
So take, so take our hand, our hand
La, la, la-la-la
La, la, come, let's play!
Hello, LA!
Hold to fart, not very farts, and Shaq's greatest wheat...
...my butt's too big for this seat! Ahhh!
Wow, look at it! It's so big and juicy!
How impressive! Hello everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
And me, Gigi Murin!
And together we are...
Autofister!
Well, LA, we wanted to do some LA call-and-response.
So I'm going to say something, and then you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
Hololive in LA!
Sitting in traffic!
Whatever. CCGG...
...in LA!
Okay, we're very excited to be here at Hololive Seren-skibidi?
Seren-skibidi.
Please all stand. It is 4th of July weekend, for the flag.
Please stand up, everyone!
O say can you see...
...by the dawn's early light...
...what so proud—
Okay, okay, shut up, that's enough, enough, enough...
Enough of that, enough of that shit. Okay.
How about we do a CCGG chant?
No, no, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Not yet, not yet, not yet!
USAじゃない！ No, no, no...
Not USA! No, no, no...
No, no, no, no...
Okay guys, not yet. Since you are standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus plus...
...stomping!
Stomping to the beat! Okay?
So the left side, we want them to be green!
And this side...
Green!
Orange!
Orange! Do it now!
Quickly.
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect!
Orange. Good.
Okay, okay, stomping...
And you stomp, and then we say CCGG CCGG...
Yes.
CC! GG!
Madness!
Autofister!
And then...
CC! GG!
Madness!
Come, let's play!
All right, 一緒に, together!
All right, together, together!
Everyone together! Really fast though.
Show... impress us, okay?
Okay. Are you ready? Are you ready?
Okay.
CC GG CC GG CC GG madness!
CC GG CC GG Autofister!
CC GG CC GG come, let's play!
Really impressive, guys! That was really, really good.
Maybe America is awesome.
USA!
USA! USA!
Yeah, they freaking love us again...
...in America!
In America! Well, for those at home...
...this is sadly the end of the free section. So please...
There's one more song actually.
Oh, there's one more song! One more song! Sorry, sorry, sorry...
Um, but there's the streaming tickets down below, so please check them out.
In the description. Check out the streaming tickets, okay?
Autofister forgot to do this today, okay?
And 無料配信は次の曲で最後になります！
And the free broadcast ends with the next song!
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
Be sure to buy a stream ticket to watch the rest of the live show!
買って見てね！
Buy a ticket and watch!
Or you hate us. Or you freaking hate us, okay?
Don't hate us. Don't be a freaking loser.
Don't hate us. For the very last part...
...since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
So...
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you!
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin!
And we need you to chant "Serendipity", right?
Okay?
Keep chanting until we leave, okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone!
Don't stop!
Okay. Well, one time together, everyone!
Serendipity!
Wheee! Wheee!
I'll be your exit route
Pound the gavel and sentence me to doom
Even though I'm just doing what you do
Decide which lies become truth
No, you never really thought about it that far
Judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
That's the price that I pay, it's a deep mark
Come, pick your sacrifice
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected and not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
When you...
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
One request, it's: hypocrisy
I've seen what you do in private rings
All your friends, yeah they know whatcha really think
To your glory, the masses keep on singing
Point at me in a hurry
Pick a scapegoat for the new controversy
Even when I'm buried, hidden, silent, you'll be wary
Please dear God show them mercy
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected and not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
When you...
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Break me now
Take me down
Me down
One request, it's:
I see your sins
And they're in your soul, consume and ignore
Decay to your core
I'll never win to you
But within you'll...
And when I...
You will...
And in your hands, the hammer pounds the nail in
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
When you...
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
One request, it's:
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light
One time in a lifetime
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true
One time in a lifetime
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads, so many journeys
But luck decided that today, we'd meet
It's serendipity
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (that's right)
One time in a lifetime
One magic moment that we share
While music lingers in the air
A song of everlasting bonds
One time in a lifetime
To warm my heart as time goes on
Each day will bring another journey
With new encounters that are meant to be
It's serendipity
Miraculous, that we're together in this life
A perfect dance of happenstance that brought us side by side
It's marvelous that though the universe is wide
You're standing here beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (that's right)
One time in a lifetime
This is right where we're meant to be
Sweet, sweet serendipity
Wishing on stars and chasing after dreams
Seeing where they lead
Say it with me, everybody
Serendipity
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
We'll shine like shooting stars in flight tonight
One time in a lifetime (that's right)
One time in a lifetime